# CHRISTINA XAMIN

#### CONTACT

xaminc@sheridancollege.ca



(416)-523-3132



www.christinaxamin.com

2232 Wuthering Heights Way Oakville, ON, Canada L6M 0A3

#### SKILLS

- Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite
- Confident working with both Macs and PCs, as well as their accompanying software (Microsoft Office, iWork, etc.)
- Understanding of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Excels in use of social media outlets (including Twitter, Instagram, Facebook, YouTube. Pinterest and Tumblr)
- Ability to work in a team with a wide range of people
- Able to make decisions and work through problems
- Manages time effectively
- · Easily adapts to new situations
- · Presents ideas and opinions in an open and unbiased way

#### CERTIFICATIONS

CPR Level C + AED

Ambitious designer with 4+ years experience in a professional design environment. Currently working towards a Bachelor of Interaction Design degree. Highly proficient in graphic design. video editing and web design software. Background in visual and creative arts using both traditional and digital elements.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor of Interaction Design** Sheridan College

September 2014- Present

## **Creativity and Creative Problem Solving Certificate** Sheridan College

September 2014 - Present

## **Visual and Creative Arts Advanced Diploma Sheridan College**

January 2012 - May 2014

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## SOCIAL MEDIA/ DIGITAL BRANDING INTERN **Crowell Lane Creative, New York, NY (Remote position)** May 2016- September 2016

- Designed and researched social media content for brands
- Worked with team to develop promotional campaigns

## **GRAPHIC DESIGN ASSISTANT (CONTRACT)** Oakville Public Library, Oakville, ON

May 2016- August 2016

- · Created various promotional material for print, web and environmental applications
- Maintained a graphic consistency by adhering to the library's visual identity and AODA compliancy
- Provided branding and graphic support for the 2016 TD Summer Reading Program.

## **GRAPHIC DESIGNER (CONTRACT)** AFL Canada, Toronto, ON

November 2013- March 2014

- Designed Men and Women's International Cup jerseys
- Created design mockups catered towards clients needs